export const questions = [
  {
    question:
      "🎤 Where did we go when we went out only with the both of us for the first time?",
    choices: ["🎶 Singing", "🐶 Pet cafe", "🌳 Park", "🎬 Movie"],
    correctAnswer: "🎶 Singing",
  },
  {
    question: "👀 What's the first thing I noticed about you?",
    choices: ["😍 Your eyes", "😊 Smile", "😂 Laugh", "👗 Style"],
    correctAnswer: "😍 Your eyes",
  },
  {
    question: "💡 What's the most important lesson I've learned from you?",
    choices: ["⏳ Patience", "💖 Kindness", "❤️ Love", "✨ Leaving no regrets"],
    correctAnswer: "✨ Leaving no regrets",
  },
  {
    question: "⭐ What’s the quality I admire most about you?",
    choices: [
      "🌍 Your willingness to explore",
      "🗣️ Your honesty",
      "🎨 Your creativity",
      "🤝 Your loyalty",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "🌍 Your willingness to explore",
  },
  {
    question: "💞 What’s my favorite way you show me you love me?",
    choices: [
      "💌 Through words",
      "🤗 Through actions",
      "🎁 Through surprises",
      "🤍 Through touch",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "🤍 Through touch",
  },
  {
    question: "💋 Where did our first kiss happen?",
    choices: ["🚗 Car", "🌳 Park", "🎓 University", "🛍️ Shopping mall"],
    correctAnswer: "🚗 Car",
  },
  {
    question: "📅 What month did we meet each other?",
    choices: ["❄️ Feb", "🌸 Jan", "🌷 April", "☀️ June"],
    correctAnswer: "❄️ Feb",
  },
  {
    question: "🍦 What’s our favorite flavor of ice cream?",
    choices: ["🍨 Vanilla", "🍫 Chocolate", "🌿 Mint", "🍓 Strawberry"],
    correctAnswer: "🌿 Mint",
  },
  {
    question: "🎄 What’s my favorite festive season?",
    choices: [
      "🌙 Hari Raya",
      "🎅 Christmas",
      "🧧 Chinese New Year",
      "🎃 Halloween",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "🎅 Christmas",
  },
  {
    question: "💬 What’s the most important thing about our relationship?",
    choices: [
      "🗣️ Our communication",
      "😂 Our laughter",
      "🌍 Our adventures",
      "🤝 Our trust",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "🗣️ Our communication",
  },
  {
    question: "📈 What’s my favorite way you’ve helped me grow as a person?",
    choices: [
      "💪 By encouraging me",
      "🔥 By challenging me",
      "🤗 By supporting me",
      "🌟 By believing in me",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "🔥 By challenging me",
  },
  {
    question: "🌈 What's the first thing I like about your personality?",
    choices: [
      "😊 Your sense of humor",
      "💡 Your creativity",
      "🧠 Your intelligence",
      "❤️ Your kindness",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "❤️ Your kindness",
  },
  {
    question: "🍦 What’s my least favorite ice cream flavor?",
    choices: ["🍓 Strawberry", "🍫 Chocolate", "🍋 Lemon", "🌰 Hazelnut"],
    correctAnswer: "🍫 Chocolate",
  },
  {
    question: "📈 How do you make me feel more confident in myself?",
    choices: [
      "🔥 By motivating me",
      "🌟 By complimenting me",
      "💪 By empowering me",
      "🤗 By being there for me",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "🤗 By being there for me",
  },
  {
    question: "🍽️ What’s my favorite type of cuisine?",
    choices: ["🍕 Italian", "🍣 Korean", "🍔 American", "🌮 Mexican"],
    correctAnswer: "🍣 Korean",
  },
  {
    question: "🎬 What's the first movie/series we watched together?",
    choices: ["🎥 破地狱", "❤️ 骗骗喜欢你", "🦑 Squid Game", "👾 Don't know"],
    correctAnswer: "🎥 破地狱",
  },
  {
    question: "🍔 What's my favorite fast food restaurant?",
    choices: ["🍔 Burger King", "🍕 Domino's", "🍟 McDonald's", "🌮 Taco Bell"],
    correctAnswer: "🍕 Domino's",
  },
  {
    question: "🎉 What’s my favorite way to celebrate special occasions?",
    choices: [
      "🎂 Party with friends",
      "🍽️ Dinner date",
      "🎁 Surprises",
      "🏖️ Vacation",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "🏖️ Vacation",
  },
  {
    question: "🏡 What's my dream home location?",
    choices: [
      "🌊 Beachfront",
      "🏞️ Mountain cabin",
      "🏙️ City apartment",
      "🌳 Countryside",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "🌊 Beachfront",
  },
  {
    question: "🍩 What's my favorite dessert?",
    choices: ["🍫 Chocolate cake", "🍦 Ice cream", "🍩 Donuts", "🍪 Cookies"],
    correctAnswer: "🍦 Ice cream",
  },
  {
    question: "🌞 Where would I love to travel next?",
    choices: ["🌴 Bali", "🏙️ Tokyo", "🏝️ Maldives", "🌍 New Zealand"],
    correctAnswer: "🏙️🌍 New Zealand",
  },
  {
    question: "💼 What’s my dream job?",
    choices: [
      "🎬 Actor/Actress",
      "🖥️ Tech entrepreneur",
      "✈️ Travel blogger",
      "🧑🏼‍🌾 Farmer",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "🧑🏼‍🌾 Farmer",
  },
  {
    question: "💌 What’s my love language?",
    choices: [
      "💖 Words of affirmation",
      "🤗 Physical touch",
      "🎁 Receiving gifts",
      "🌍 Acts of service",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "🤗 Physical touch",
  },
  {
    question: "🧘‍♀️ What's my go-to way to relax?",
    choices: [
      "📚 Reading a book",
      "🎮 Playing video games",
      "🛀 Taking a bath",
      "🏃🏻‍♂️ Running",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "🏃🏻‍♂️ Running",
  },
  {
    question: "🖼️ What's my favorite form of art?",
    choices: ["🖌️ Painting", "📸 Photography", "🎥 Film", "🎨 Sculpture"],
    correctAnswer: "📸 Photography",
  },
  {
    question: "🌇 What's my favorite time of the day?",
    choices: ["🌅 Morning", "🌞 Afternoon", "🌇 Evening", "🌙 Night"],
    correctAnswer: "🌅 Morning",
  },
  {
    question: "🌟 What's my biggest fear?",
    choices: ["🐍 Snakes", "🔥 Fire", "🌊 Drowning", "💀 Heights"],
    correctAnswer: "🐍 Snakes",
  },
  {
    question: "🍩 What's my favorite breakfast food?",
    choices: ["🥞 Pancakes", "🍳 Eggs", "🥯 Bagel", "🍩 Donuts"],
    correctAnswer: "🍳 Eggs",
  },
  {
    question: "🎮 What’s my favorite hobby to do on weekends?",
    choices: [
      "🎮 Playing video games",
      "🖥️ Coding",
      "🧳 Traveling",
      "🍳 Cooking",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "🖥️ Coding",
  },
  {
    question: "📚 What's my favorite book genre?",
    choices: ["📖 Mystery", "💔 Romance", "⚔️ Fantasy", "🎓 Non-fiction"],
    correctAnswer: "💔 Romance",
  },
  {
    question: "🏋️‍♀️ What's my favorite type of exercise?",
    choices: ["💪 Weightlifting", "🏃‍♂️ Running", "🧘‍♀️ Yoga", "🚴‍♂️ Cycling"],
    correctAnswer: "🏃‍♂️ Running",
  },
  {
    question: "🍹 What’s my go-to non-alcoholic drink?",
    choices: ["🍶 Tea", "🥤 Soft drink", "🍊 Juice", "🍵 Coffee"],
    correctAnswer: "🍵 Coffee",
  },
  {
    question: "🐾 What's my favorite animal?",
    choices: ["🐶 Dog", "🐱 Cat", "🐰 Rabbit", "🦁 Lion"],
    correctAnswer: "🐶 Dog",
  },
  {
    question: "🏆 What’s my idea of success?",
    choices: ["💰 Wealth", "🌍 Travel", "🎓 Knowledge", "💖 Love"],
    correctAnswer: "💰 Wealth",
  },
  {
    question: "🎵 What’s my favorite instrument to listen to?",
    choices: ["🎸 Guitar", "🎹 Piano", "🥁 Drums", "🎻 Violin"],
    correctAnswer: "🎸 Guitar",
  },
  {
    question: "🌳 What's my favorite outdoor activity?",
    choices: ["🏕️ Camping", "🚶‍♂️ Hiking", "🚲 Biking", "🌅 Watching the sunset"],
    correctAnswer: "🌅 Watching the sunset",
  },
];
